[
    {
        "Question": "cherish",
        "Answer": "value",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "immobile",
        "Answer": "motionless",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "explore",
        "Answer": "investigate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "emitted",
        "Answer": "released",
        "Options": "send out"
    },
    {
        "Question": "deviate",
        "Answer": "detract",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "conductive to",
        "Answer": "favorable to",
        "Options": "contributive"
    },
    {
        "Question": "crude",
        "Answer": "primitive/ unsophisticated",
        "Options": "rough/ initial"
    },
    {
        "Question": "degree",
        "Answer": "extent",
        "Options": "measure"
    },
    {
        "Question": "abolished",
        "Answer": "ended",
        "Options": "eliminated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "allied",
        "Answer": "related",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "discard",
        "Answer": "throw away",
        "Options": "throw up"
    },
    {
        "Question": "resume",
        "Answer": "restart",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "his imitator",
        "Answer": "the people who copied hime",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "interpreted",
        "Answer": "understood",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "manipulated",
        "Answer": "skillfully used",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "displace",
        "Answer": "move out of position",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "differing",
        "Answer": "varying",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "interplay",
        "Answer": "interaction",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sought",
        "Answer": "looked for",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sovereign",
        "Answer": "master",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "mutually beneficial",
        "Answer": "helpful to one another",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "impractical",
        "Answer": "unrealistic",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "facilitated",
        "Answer": "made easier",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "cluster",
        "Answer": "group",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "reinforce",
        "Answer": "strengthen",
        "Options": "supporting"
    },
    {
        "Question": "composed of",
        "Answer": "made up of",
        "Options": "created/ mix"
    },
    {
        "Question": "completely",
        "Answer": "totally",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "maintain",
        "Answer": "claim",
        "Options": "keep/ preserve"
    },
    {
        "Question": "switch on",
        "Answer": "activate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "astute",
        "Answer": "clever",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "whereas",
        "Answer": "while",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "exceedingly",
        "Answer": "highly",
        "Options": "extremely"
    },
    {
        "Question": "minute",
        "Answer": "tiny",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "curb",
        "Answer": "control",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "vulnerable",
        "Answer": "open to attack",
        "Options": "although"
    },
    {
        "Question": "preoccupation",
        "Answer": "concern",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "halted",
        "Answer": "stopped",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "take precedence over",
        "Answer": "have greater importance than",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "comprise",
        "Answer": "consist of",
        "Options": "make up"
    },
    {
        "Question": "alleged",
        "Answer": "supposed",
        "Options": "asserted"
    },
    {
        "Question": "boost",
        "Answer": "raise",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "further",
        "Answer": "additionally",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "emergent",
        "Answer": "developing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "engulf",
        "Answer": "swallow",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "detrimental",
        "Answer": "harmful",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "critical",
        "Answer": "fault-finding",
        "Options": "crucial/ essential"
    },
    {
        "Question": "graphically",
        "Answer": "vividly",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "document",
        "Answer": "record",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "fluctuations",
        "Answer": "variations",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "bombard",
        "Answer": "strike",
        "Options": "assault"
    },
    {
        "Question": "incite",
        "Answer": "stimulate",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "quest",
        "Answer": "search",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sentimental",
        "Answer": "emotional",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "anomaly",
        "Answer": "irregularity",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "outstanding",
        "Answer": "excellent",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "furthermore",
        "Answer": "in addition",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "out of sight",
        "Answer": "hidden",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "are preserved",
        "Answer": "survive",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "blossom",
        "Answer": "flourish",
        "Options": "thrive"
    },
    {
        "Question": "chancy",
        "Answer": "risky",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "duration",
        "Answer": "length of time",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "freeing",
        "Answer": "releasing",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "negligible",
        "Answer": "minor",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "experimental",
        "Answer": "trial",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "feasible",
        "Answer": "practical",
        "Options": "achievable"
    },
    {
        "Question": "distributed",
        "Answer": "spread",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "championed",
        "Answer": "supported",
        "Options": "promoted"
    },
    {
        "Question": "properly",
        "Answer": "appropriately",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "trappings",
        "Answer": "decorations",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "congregate",
        "Answer": "gather",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "accompany",
        "Answer": "occur along with",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "consequently",
        "Answer": "therefore",
        "Options": "as a result"
    },
    {
        "Question": "in the same breath",
        "Answer": "immediately",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "sensible",
        "Answer": "reasonable",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "divest",
        "Answer": "deprive",
        "Options": "get rid of"
    },
    {
        "Question": "determinants",
        "Answer": "causes",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "tangible",
        "Answer": "physical",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "emante",
        "Answer": "emerge",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "pronounced",
        "Answer": "strongest",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "key",
        "Answer": "essential",
        "Options": "important/ crucial"
    },
    {
        "Question": "antagonizing",
        "Answer": "angering",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "detractor",
        "Answer": "critic",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "edible",
        "Answer": "eatable",
        "Options": "things that can be eaten"
    },
    {
        "Question": "renown",
        "Answer": "fame",
        "Options": "famous"
    },
    {
        "Question": "despite",
        "Answer": "even though",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "brilliant",
        "Answer": "bright",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "eroded",
        "Answer": "worn down",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "trend",
        "Answer": "tendency",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "vigorously",
        "Answer": "strong and healthy",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "enactment",
        "Answer": "performance",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "turbulent",
        "Answer": "violent",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "coincides with",
        "Answer": "occurs at the same time as",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "dismiss",
        "Answer": "reject",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "habits",
        "Answer": "usual behaviors",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "distant",
        "Answer": "far",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "devoted",
        "Answer": "dedicated",
        "Options": "concentrated"
    },
    {
        "Question": "repudiate",
        "Answer": "reject",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "slight",
        "Answer": "small",
        "Options": ""
    },
    {
        "Question": "constant",
        "Answer": "unchanging",
        "Options": "stable/ always"
    },
    {
        "Question": "ensuing",
        "Answer": "subsequent",
        "Options": ""
    }
]